Timna Aversa

Birth Date : 10/04/1996 Citizenship : Italian / Brazilian

Address : Berlin, Germany 10625 Phone : +49 15755417345

E-mail: timnaaversa@gmail.com

I have previously worked with cleaning buildings at night, and have done some house cleaning in the beginning of my career. As someone that can efficiently complete a wide range of cleaning tasks, I clean and maintain the office, break room, bathroom, and ground floor. In addition I am an organized, service focused and meticulous team player employee.



EXPERIENCE

Aversa Consulting

11 / 2015 - 11 / 2020

- Performed Cleanings in Buildings at night.
- Dust furniture, walls, machines, and equipment.
- Managed cleaning for office areas.
- Empty all trash cans and replaced liners.
- Keep all janitorial equipment in clean, safe, and operable conditions.
- Travel to and from work sites in a timely manner.
- Maintain bathrooms and kitchen.
- Swept and mopped floors.

House Cleaning

05 / 2015 - 01 / 2016

- Experience in performing residential cleaning and housekeeping tasks.
- Knowledge of flor, equipment, and surface cleaning methods and procedures.
- Knowledge of a variety of cleaning chemicals and equipment.
- Familiarity with safety measures, cleaning standards, and customer service.
- Swep, vacuum, and mop all floor surfaces of the house.
- Dusted and wiped all lighting fixtures, shelves, mirrors, and windows of the house.
- Executed all house cleaning tasks according to established cleanliness standards agreed upon.

EDUCATION

Salt Lake Community College - *United States*

05 / 2017 - 08 / 2020

On track towards Electrical Engineer, incomplete.

CEEP High School - Brazil

01 / 2010 - 01 / 2014

LANGUAGE

Portuguese: Native

English: C2

German: A1 (Taking Classes)

PERSONAL INTEREST

Photography, I took a photography class in college and have kept it as a hobby since.

Front end web development, I took a class of programming in College and have come back to it in the last few months practicing it in my free time.